# Gabriel Danaila

WEB DEVELOPER

gabriel.danaila.tech@gmail.com www.gabrieldanaila.com www.github.com/Gabriel-Danaila

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

iDesign - Netherlands

Feb 2021 - Present

Digital Agency

#### Junior Web Developer - Freelancer

My proficiency lies in using programming languages such as HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap, having understanding of GitHub, Command Line Interface (CLI), API and backend development for server-side applications using Visual Studio Code as my code editor of choice.

Testing code across multiple browsers and platforms to ensure optimal functionality, I maintain a constant focus on writing clean code while continually enhancing my knowledge and skills.

Across my diverse portfolio, I have worked on a range of projects including server and database integrated applications, development of structured and responsive landing pages designed to meet specific client specifications.

Nissan - USA

Feb 2011 - Feb 2019

Battery Manufacturing Plant for Electric Vehicles

## Maintenance Engineer Technician

I was responsible for maintaining automated equipment, using program backups, PLC diagnostic software, and perform calibration for cameras and sensors. Expertise in operating Omron Programmable Logic Controllers and managing Omron Vision System hardware and software

Proficiency in operating Mitsubishi and Yamaha industrial robots at the Nissan Battery Manufacturing Plant for Electric Vehicles

Leviton - USA

Feb 2010 - Feb 2011

Warehouse and Distribution Center Facilities

## Maintenance Engineer Technician

I've actively engaged in the adoption of concepts such as Kaizen implementation, Root Cause Analysis for major Breakdown Reports, Corrective - Preventive - Predictive Maintenance, the 5S methodology designed to foster a quality work environment - Sort, Set in Order, Shine, Standardize, Sustain

Cinram - USA

Feb 2007 - Feb 2009

Warehouse and Distribution Center Facilities

## Maintenance Engineer Technician

Architect of the Standard Operation Sheet Procedure (SOS), One Point Lessons for recurring tasks, standard steps, and resource identification for efficient task execution

#### HIGHLIGHTS

10 + years of experience applying my extensive experience in process engineering to web development. I make the transition seamlessly from the production line to lines of code and from complex industrial robots to creating modern, reliable websites and applications

# SKILLS

- HTML
- · CSS
- JavaScript
- Bootstrap
- · Visual Studio Code
- Node
- GitHub
- Figma
- Writing clean code
- · Problem Solving

## Work recognitions

- Battery Recognition Emblem Plate for Work Ethics - Nissan 2103
- Best Employee Recognition Award -Leviton 2012
- Perfect Attendance Award for Leviton 2011 / 2012

### **EDUCATION**

Science Degree in Engineering (SIA) -Technology and Quality Control. University of Galati , 1998 – 2004

# LANGUAGES

English – Fluent Romanian - Fluent Spanish, Italian - Intermediate